Brayan Sanchez

Software Developer

leon16.bs@gmail.com | clouddcoder.github.io/portfolio

EXPERIENCE

Universidad del Valle — *Software Developer*

APRIL 2020 - JANUARY 2023 | CALI, COLOMBIA

Improved the design and functionality of the university's software for students and professors, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript y PHP.

Abbott — *Internship*

JUNE 2017 - JUNE 2018 | CALI, COLOMBIA

Performed administrative tasks as an office assistant

PROJECTS

E-commerce Lottus

Electronic commerce built with React, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL and Docker. Implements features such as user authentication, product catalog, shopping cart, checkout and wishlist. The back-end is deployed in GCP.

Task manager

Web app built with Node.js, Express, EJS, CSS, PostgreSQL and Docker that creates and deletes tasks, moreover, it selects those that have already been done to keep an organized list.

Weather app

Web app built with React, JavaScript, CSS and Tailwind that provides weather information of any city using the OpenWeatherMap API.

SUMMARY

Software Developer with 1 year of experience developing scalable and user-friendly web applications.

SKILLS

Programming languages

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Astro

Technologies

React, Docker, Linux, Express, Material UI, Jest, GCP, Nginx

Tools

Git, GitHub, Notion, Asana, Slack, Trello

EDUCATION

Universidad del Valle

AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT Systems engineering student

CECEP

AUGUST 2016 - JANUARY 2020 Industrial Technologist